<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on And Zero at the Bone</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on And Zero at the Bone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 -- 2017. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 07:40:51 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Seed post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/anoffice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 07:40:51 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/anoffice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been years since I have worked at a place where I&amp;rsquo;ve had an office of my
own. In fact, only two of the eight jobs I&amp;rsquo;ve had since finishing schools
have featured this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first job teaching physics at a college  was the only one where I had an
actual room with bookshelves and a desk and a phone of my own. I also had a
lab with benches and cupboards and could ask the departmental secretary and
the departmental machinist for help. From time to time I would be supervising
a student or two on research, never as a teaching assistant, unfortunately,
since the grading load turned out to be more than I liked, and I served on my
share of faculty committees as well. Of course I didn&amp;rsquo;t really know what I
was doing, not for a long time. I had office hours where students could come
around for help, though of course few did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only other job where I technically had an office was the three years I ran
my own business fixing furniture in between tech gigs, working out of my house.
I did the books, called customers, paid the bills, ordered supplies, and
carried out the whole thing as a one-man operation basically, though I was
a franchisee. With the strict IRS guidelines for home offices in place, I didn&amp;rsquo;t
try to claim deductions for my office or my garage shop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All my other jobs involved sharing an office, working out of a cubicle,
working in an open-plan space, or working remotely at a site without an
assigned place for my stuff. Not unusual for the way things work nowadays, as
compared to the ways business was carried out when I was growing up. Only
executives and bona-fide professionals (doctors and lawyers and accountants)
get a room of their own where they could put their credentials up on a wall
and shut the door on a world not privy to the powerful things they need to
do, and I&amp;rsquo;ve abandoned any attempt to follow that path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do I think you&amp;rsquo;re a better person if you work in an office? No. Do I feel
cheated for not having had my own office except for the two exceptions in
my lifetime? Not that much, though I think maybe I could have accomplished
a bit more in a place away from the hubbub, more for my employers, not for
myself. It&amp;rsquo;s just that the new way is to shrink the office down to a small
cabinet and the space between one&amp;rsquo;s earphones, for a lot of white-collar
workers, and that&amp;rsquo;s just the way it&amp;rsquo;s going to be from now on.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seed post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/newblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 20:18:51 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/newblog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m starting this personal blog as a successor to my previous blogs:
* &lt;a href=&#34;http://t2o.blogspot.com&#34;&gt;Heavy Heavy Water&lt;/a&gt;
* &lt;a href=&#34;http://poorpoorthing.posterous.com&#34;&gt;Poor Poor Thing&lt;/a&gt;
* &lt;a href=&#34;http://frabjoustimes.magahiz.com&#34;&gt;Frabjous Times&lt;/a&gt;
* &lt;a href=&#34;http://evilhow.com&#34;&gt;evilHow&lt;/a&gt;
* &lt;a href=&#34;http://upperrh.wordpress.com&#34;&gt;Worlds in the Upper Right Hand Corner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have some ideas of stashing some of my tech work here, links to my creative
stuff, pointers to things I&amp;rsquo;ve found on the web, and other miscellaneous items.
I have been on &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/richmagahiz&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/richard.magahiz&#34;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;
and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pinterest.com/richardmagahiz/&#34;&gt;Pinterest&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/rmagahiz&#34;&gt;Linkedin&lt;/a&gt; for a while now,
but it seems like social media has mostly resisted the idea of sharing content
outside of their walled gardens. It sure makes it hard to find the things
I have shared in the past without heroic efforts. So someplace where I can
put up whatever items come to mind and control on my own is attractive.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>